Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files, 1965-2011 TJU.2010.01.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Research Files, 1967-2010; II.
  - Interior and Environment, 1980-2006; 9.
    - Gettysburg Address Exhibition, 1991-1994 (Box 279, Folder 13-14)
    - Gettysburg Boundary Bill, 1989-1990 (Box 279, Folder 15)
    - Gettysburg College, Land exchange, 1994-1995 (Box 279, Folder 16-17)
    - Gettysburg pollution, 1985 (Box 279, Folder 18)
    - Great Lakes region environmental management, 1985 (Box 279, Folder 19)
    - Hazardous wastes and superfund, 1982-1983 (Box 279, Folder 20-21)
    - Independence National Historic Park, 1990 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Independence National Historic Park and National Constitution Center, 1988-1997 (Box 280, Folder 2-4)
    - Indoor Air Quality Act, 1991 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Interstate waste issues, 1993-1995 (Box 280, Folder 6-11)
    - Leahy-Collins mercury resolution, 2005 (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - Liberty Bell Complex project, 1998-1999 (Box 280, Folder 13)
    - Low-Income Home Energy Assistance Program (LIHEAP), 1984 (Box 280, Folder 14)
    - Lumbee Tribe, 1992-1994 (Box 280, Folder 15)
    - Meadville Mall expansion, 1992-1994 (Box 280, Folder 16)
    - Metals recovery study, 1992-1993 (Box 280, Folder 17)
    - Mine Safety and Health Administration (MSHA), Quecreek mining accident, 2002-2003 (Box 280, Folder 18)
    - National Museum of American Jewish History, 1998-1999 (Box 280, Folder 19)
    - National Nuclear Waste Policy Act, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 20)
    - National Nuclear Waste Policy Act, 1981 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - National Underground Railroad Freedom Center, 1999 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Natural gas, 1981-1983 (Box 281, Folder 3-6)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, Three Mile Island, 1983 (Box 281, Folder 7-8)
    - Nuclear waste storage, 1994 (Box 281, Folder 9)
    - Offshore oil and gas issues, Equitable resources, 1994 (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - Offshore drilling votes, 1995 (Box 281, Folder 11)
    - Ohio Power electric utility case, 1994-1995 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - Old Faithful Protection Act, Yellowstone, 1994 (Box 281, Folder 13)
    - Paoli Battlefield, National Park Service (NPS) legislation, 1998 (Box 281, Folder 14)
    - Paoli Railyard, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 15)
    - Paoli Railyard, Civil suits, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 16)
    - Paoli Railyard, Memos and talking points, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 17)
    - Paoli Railyard, Newsclips, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 18)
    - Paoli Railyard, James Seif letter to Specter, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 19)
    - Paoli Railyard, Specter letters to Lee Thomas, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 20)
    - Paoli Railyard, Specter notices of civil action, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 21)
    - Paoli Railyard, Timelines, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 22)
    - PECO/PP&L merger, 1995 (Box 281, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission, 1997 (Box 281, Folder 24)
    - Petroleum Marketing Practices Act amendments, 1994 (Box 281, Folder 25)
    - Piper Aviation Museum, 1997-1998 (Box 281, Folder 26)
    - Pollution, 1980-1982 (Box 281, Folder 27)
    - Power Marketing Administrations, 1995 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Predator control and poison, 1982 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Rainbow Family Gathering, 1998-1999 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Reclamation Reform Act, 1982 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Reinvention of the Forest Service, 1995 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Resource Conservation and Recovery Act, 1982-1993 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Judith Rodin, 1998 (Box 282, Folder 7)
    - Rosenbach Museum and Library, 1997 (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - John Shutak, MSHA, 1993 (Box 282, Folder 9)
    - Specter correspondence with corporations, 1994-1995 (Box 282, Folder 10-11)
    - Specter environmental voting scorecards, 1989-2006 (Box 282, Folder 12-13)
    - Specter's amendment to H.R. 3708, 2000 (Box 282, Folder 14)
    - Superfund, 1986-1990 (Box 282, Folder 15)
    - Superfund, 1994-1999 (Box 282, Folder 16)
    - Superfund, Clean air letter, 1997 (Box 282, Folder 17)
    - Superfund, Letters and memos, 1994 (Box 282, Folder 18)
    - Superfund, Liability assignment, 2000-2003 (Box 282, Folder 19)
    - Superfund, Minor Party Liability Relief Act, 1997 (Box 282, Folder 20)
    - Superfund, Pennsylvania sites, 1992-2001 (Box 282, Folder 21)
    - Superfund, Recycling, 1999 (Box 282, Folder 22)
    - Superfund, Recycling equity, 1999-2005 (Box 282, Folder 23)
    - Superfund, S. 8, 1997 (Box 282, Folder 24)
    - Superfund, S. 1742, 1995-1997 (Box 282, Folder 25)
    - Superfund, Specter legislative work, 1994-1998 (Box 282, Folder 26-27)
    - Three Mile Island disaster, 1981-1982 (Box 282, Folder 28-30)
    - Three Mile Island disaster investigation, 1983-1984 (Box 283, Folder 1-13)
    - Three Mile Island disaster investigation, 1983-1984 (Box 284, Folder 1-3)
    - Underground Railroad, 1996-1998 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Urban Agenda Act, 2001 (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Urban and community forestry, 1996-1998 (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Ward Valley Land Transfer Act, 1994 (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - Waste flow control, 1994-1995 (Box 284, Folder 8-9)
    - Waste Technologies hazardous waste incinerator, 1991-1997 (Box 284, Folder 10-13)
    - White Clay Creek, 1990-1996 (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - White Clay Creek, 1998 (Box 284, Folder 15)
    - Woodmont National Historic Landmark, 1998 (Box 284, Folder 16)
    - Youth and Yound Adult Conservation Corps, 1981 (Box 284, Folder 17)
  - Labor, 1980-2009; 10.
    The Labor subseries includes material on the National Labor Relations Board, the Employee Free Choice Act, and other related topics.
    - Air Traffic Controllers Association, 2005 (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Alternative work schedules, 1980-1982 (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union Legislative Conference, 2005 (Box 285, Folder 3)
    - American Apparel Manufacturer's Association, 1996 (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - American Conservation Corps, 1982 (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), 2005 (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1986-1996 (Box 285, Folder 7-8)
    - AFL-CIO, Asbestos legislation, 2005 (Box 285, Folder 9)
    - AFL-CIO, Contacts list, 2008 (Box 285, Folder 10)
    - AFL-CIO, Convention, 2005 (Box 285, Folder 11)
    - AFL-CIO, Labor breakfast, Philadelphia, 2007 (Box 285, Folder 12)
    - AFL-CIO, Questionnaire, 2004 (Box 285, Folder 13)
    - American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada immigration issues, 2005 (Box 285, Folder 14)
    - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 2009 (Box 285, Folder 15)
    - American Franchisee Association, 1995-1999 (Box 285, Folder 16)
    - American Postal Workers Union, 1995-1996 (Box 285, Folder 17)
    - American Postal Workers Union, 2007 (Box 285, Folder 18)
    - Amish labor issues, 1997-1999 (Box 285, Folder 19-20)
    - Amish labor issues, 2003-2004 (Box 285, Folder 21)
    - Amtrak labor costs report, 2003 (Box 285, Folder 22)
    - Amtrak Philadelphia Clocker Commuter Rail Service elimination, 2005 (Box 285, Folder 23)
    - Associated Builders and Contractors (ABC) labor issues, 1996-1997 (Box 285, Folder 24)
    - Association of Civilian Technicians, 1993 (Box 285, Folder 25)
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation, 1992 (Box 285, Folder 26)
    - Beverly Enterprises Service Employees International Union (SEIU) striker replacement, 1995-1996 (Box 285, Folder 27-28)
    - Black lung disability trust fund, 1981 (Box 285, Folder 29)
    - Building Construction and Trades Department, 2001-2006 (Box 285, Folder 30)
    - Building and construction trades prevailing wage, 1993 (Box 285, Folder 31)
    - Mark Carmel, Labor memos, 2004 (Box 285, Folder 32)
    - Caterpillar York plant shutdown and United Auto Workers (UAW), 1996 (Box 285, Folder 33)
    - Central American Free Trade Agreement (CAFTA) and AFL-CIO, 2005 (Box 285, Folder 34)
    - Coal Industry Retiree Health Benefit Act (Reachback), 1992 (Box 285, Folder 35-38)
    - Coal Industry Retiree Health Benefit Act (Reachback), 1992 (Box 286, Folder 1-2)
    - Coal reachback taxes, 1994-1995 (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Comp Time Bill, 1997 (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Comparable worth and pay equity issues, 1984 (Box 286, Folder 5-6)
    - Comprehensive Employment Training Act of 1978 allocation, 1982 (Box 286, Folder 7)
    - Davis-Bacon Act reform, 1994-1996 (Box 286, Folder 8-14)
    - Delaware Valley Healthcare Coalition tax exempt status, 2004 (Box 286, Folder 15)
    - DOD National Security Personnel System, 2005-2006 (Box 286, Folder 16)
    - DOD Worker Coalition, 2005 (Box 286, Folder 17)
    - Department of Labor (DOL) annual report, 1982 (Box 286, Folder 18)
    - DOL reorganization, 1995 (Box 286, Folder 19)
    - Discrimination in workforce, Executive Order 11246, 1985 (Box 286, Folder 20)
    - Displaced homemakers, 1996 (Box 286, Folder 21)
    - Double-breasting construction industry labor issue, 1996 (Box 286, Folder 22)
    - Dyncorp and United States Postal Service (USPS), 1996 (Box 286, Folder 23)
    - Economically targeted investments, 1995 (Box 286, Folder 24)
    - Employee Free Choice Act, 2005-2007 (Box 287, Folder 1-5)
    - Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974 Clarification Act, 1995-1996 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Employee stock ownership plans, 1994 (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - Employment Policy Foundation, Wage issues, 1996 (Box 287, Folder 8)
    - Employment and Training Report of the President, 1981 (Box 287, Folder 9)
    - Employment training systems reform and partnerships, 1981-1982 (Box 287, Folder 10-12)
    - Ergonomics legislation, 1995 (Box 287, Folder 13)
    - Family and Medical Leave Act (FMLA), 1981 (Box 287, Folder 14)
    - FMLA, 2005 (Box 287, Folder 15-16)
    - FMLA, Change of definition, 2005 (Box 287, Folder 17)
    - Federal Bureau of Prisons, 2004-2005 (Box 287, Folder 18-19)
    - Federal government, Service Task Force, 1989 (Box 287, Folder 20)
    - Federal job outsourcing, 2003-2005 (Box 287, Folder 21)
    - Financial Women International and Fair Pay Act, 1995-1996 (Box 287, Folder 22)
    - General Dynamics Scranton plant closure, 1996 (Box 287, Folder 23)
    - General Motors plant closure, West Mifflin, 2005 (Box 287, Folder 24)
    - Graduate student labor hearing, 2004 (Box 287, Folder 25)
    - Hope Ministries Senior Workforce Development Initiative, 2006 (Box 287, Folder 26)
    - Industrial Truck Association, 1993 (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - International Association of Firefighters, 1996 (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - International Association of Firefighters, 2005 (Box 288, Folder 3)
    - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 2009 (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, 1996 (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1993 (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, 2008 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - International Longshoreman John McCann, 1997 (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - Job Corps, 1995 (Box 288, Folder 9-12)
    - Job Corps, 1995-1996 (Box 288, Folder 13-15)
    - Job Corps, Expansion issues, 1994-1997 (Box 288, Folder 16-19)
    - Job tax credits, Specter and Heinz bills, 1982 (Box 288, Folder 20)
    - Job training legislation, 1982 (Box 288, Folder 21)
    - Job Training Partnership Act, 1991-1992 (Box 288, Folder 22-25)
    - Labor breakfast notes, 2007 (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Labor and job training reports, 1980-1982 (Box 289, Folder 2-3)
    - Labrer's International Union of North America and Arctic Wildlife Refuge, 1995 (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Life Science Career Alliance high-growth job training initiative, 2004 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Local Empowerment and Flexibility Act, 1996 (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - Maglev, DOL proposal, 2006 (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Manpower studies, 1981 (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Marcus Hook Oil Refinery, Oil Chemical and Atomic Workers Union, 1996 (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Mead Corporation packaging plant shutdown, 1996 (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Mine Safety and Health Administration, Richard Stickler Assistant Secretary nomination, 2005-2006 (Box 289, Folder 11-13)
    - Minimum wage legislation, 1995-1996 (Box 289, Folder 14-16)
    - Minimum wage legislation, 2005 (Box 289, Folder 17)
    - Minimum wage legislation, 2006-2007 (Box 289, Folder 18-19)
    - Mittal Steel trade adjustment assistance application, 2005 (Box 289, Folder 20)
    - Multiemployer pension, health, and welfare plans, 1996 (Box 289, Folder 21)
    - National Association of Chain Manufacturers, 1992-1993 (Box 289, Folder 22)
    - National Association of Letter Carriers, 1996 (Box 289, Folder 23)
    - National Association of Postal Supervisors, 1989 (Box 289, Folder 24)
    - National Association of Postmasters of the United States., 1985 (Box 289, Folder 25)
    - National Association of Postmasters of the United States., 1996 (Box 289, Folder 26)
    - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1980-1981 (Box 289, Folder 27)
    - NLRB, Sarah Fox nomination, 1996 (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - NLRB, Issues, 1996 (Box 290, Folder 2-4)
    - NLRB, Single location bargaining units, 1995-1996 (Box 290, Folder 5)
    - National Rural Letter Carriers Association, 1989 (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - National supported work demonstration study, 1981 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - National Tooling and Machining Association, 1981 (Box 290, Folder 8)
    - National Treasury Employees Union, 1994 (Box 290, Folder 9)
    - National Treasury Employees Union, 2006-2007 (Box 290, Folder 10)
    - Naval Sea Systems Command Shipbuilding Support Office closure, 2005-2006 (Box 290, Folder 11)
    - Northeastern States Fire Consortium, 1996 (Box 290, Folder 12)
    - Northwest Pennsylvania Training Partnership Consortium, 1994 (Box 290, Folder 13)
    - OSHA, Asbestos statements, 2005 (Box 290, Folder 14)
    - OSHA, Issues and reform, 1995-1997 (Box 290, Folder 15-16)
    - Office of Employment Security, 1981 (Box 290, Folder 17)
    - Older Americans Act, 1991 (Box 290, Folder 18)
    - Older Americans Act, Community service employment program, 1982 (Box 290, Folder 19)
    - On-stop skills centers, 1992 (Box 290, Folder 20)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Centers of America, Job training hearing, 1993 (Box 290, Folder 21)
    - Overtime legislation, 2005 (Box 290, Folder 22-24)
    - Pennsylvania dislocated worker funding, 1996 (Box 290, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania Labor Management Network, 1996 (Box 290, Folder 26)
    - Pennsylvania letter carriers, 1991 (Box 290, Folder 27)
    - Pennsylvania Strikebreaker Act, 1992 (Box 290, Folder 28)
    - Pension/401(k) retirement issues, 1996-1997 (Box 290, Folder 29-30)
    - Philadelphia postal workers, 1989 (Box 290, Folder 31)
    - Philadelphia Youth Service Corps, 1989 (Box 290, Folder 32)
    - Plant closings, 1987 (Box 290, Folder 33)
    - Polyvision, Clymer and Dixonville facility closures, 2005 (Box 290, Folder 34)
    - Private Sector Opportunities Act, 1981-1982 (Box 290, Folder 35)
    - Professional Air Traffic Controllers Organization, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Public Safety Employer-Employee Cooperation Act, 1999 (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Railroad Retirement Board, 1980-1982 (Box 291, Folder 3-4)
    - Railroad Retirement System, 1989 (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Railroad unemployment benefits legislation, 1992 (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - Regional Learning Alliance at Cranberry Woods, Slippery Rock University, 2004-2005 (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - Remediation strategy study and Robert Taggart training, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 8)
    - Retired Coal Miner Health Benefits Preservation Act and Bankruptcy Reform Bill, 2005 (Box 291, Folder 9)
    - Right-to-work legislation, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 10)
    - Right-to-work legislation, 1996 (Box 291, Folder 11)
    - Rockwell International New Castle facility closure, 1990 (Box 291, Folder 12)
    - Rocky Flats Nuclear Facility worker benefits, 2005 (Box 291, Folder 13)
    - Salting legislation, 1996 (Box 291, Folder 14)
    - Saturn plant, 1985 (Box 291, Folder 15)
    - Scranton Building and Construction Trades Council, 1996 (Box 291, Folder 16)
    - Service Contract Act, Proposed changes, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 17)
    - SEIU, Meeting, 1995 (Box 291, Folder 18)
    - SEIU, Northeastern Pennsylvania hospitals, 2005 (Box 291, Folder 19)
    - SEIU, Wyoming Valley, Pennsylvania Healthcare System, 2004-2006 (Box 291, Folder 20)
    - Small Business Association 8A Program, Minority set-asides, 1985-1986 (Box 291, Folder 21-22)
    - Society for Human Resource Management, 1996 (Box 291, Folder 23)
    - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 24)
    - Specialty steel, 1983 (Box 291, Folder 25)
    - Specter labor positions overview, 2004 (Box 291, Folder 26)
    - Specter Medicaid statement, 2005 (Box 291, Folder 27)
    - Specter voting record, AFL-CIO, 2007 (Box 291, Folder 28)
    - Steel bill, Background materials, 1982 (Box 291, Folder 29)
    - Steel import policies, 1984-1985 (Box 291, Folder 30)
    - Striker replacement legislation and Clinton Executive Order, 1991-1996 (Box 291, Folder 31-32)
    - Subminimum wage, 1981 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Summer youth employment programs, 1992-1993 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Larry Summers, Deputy Treasury Secretary confirmation, 1999 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Supported work evaluation final benefit-cost analysis, 1981 (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Teamsters, 1996 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters, 1997 (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Teamsters election, 1992 (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Teamsters, Literacy training, 1989-1990 (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Teamsters, Specter speech, 1996 (Box 292, Folder 9)
    - TOSCO-BP merger, 1996 (Box 292, Folder 10)
    - Trade adjustment assistance determinations, 2007 (Box 292, Folder 11)
    - Transitions toward Excellence in Achievment and Mobility (TEAM) Act, 1995-1996 (Box 292, Folder 12-15)
    - Unemployment compensation extension, 1982 (Box 292, Folder 16)
    - Unemployment insurance, 1991 (Box 292, Folder 17)
    - Unemployment legislation, 1991-1993 (Box 292, Folder 18-19)
    - Unemployment mass mailings, 1985 (Box 292, Folder 20)
    - Union Pacific-BWME rail dispute, 1996 (Box 292, Folder 21)
    - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, 1996 (Box 292, Folder 22)
    - United Auto Workers (UAW), 1996 (Box 292, Folder 23)
    - United Domestic Workers of America, 2005 (Box 292, Folder 24)
    - United Food and Commercial Workers (UFCW), 1996 (Box 292, Folder 25)
    - United Transportation Union and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 2002-2007 (Box 292, Folder 26)
    - Union membership statistics., 2007 (Box 292, Folder 27)
    - United Steelworkers, 1995 (Box 292, Folder 28)
    - Wendy's restaurants, 1996 (Box 292, Folder 29)
    - Women's Bureau, 1981 (Box 292, Folder 30)
    - Women's pensions and retirement, 1993-1997 (Box 292, Folder 31)
    - Women's pensions and retirement, 1993-1997 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Workability and work-related injuries, 1996 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Workers' Right to Choose, 2007 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Workforce Innovation Networks DOL projects, 2005 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Workforce Investment Partnership Act, 1998 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Workforce projections, 1981-1982 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Youth employment issues, 1981 (Box 293, Folder 7-8)
    - Youth violence labor initiatives, 2005 (Box 293, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Topics, 1967-2010; 11.
    The Miscellaneous Topics subseries includes material on a variety of topics of interest to Specter that do not fall into the other series reflected here, including disaster response, the Flight 93 memorial, and a number of other issues.
    - Absentee ballot controversy, Military ballots, 2004 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Accomplishments, Agriculture, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Accomplishments, Allentown, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Accomplishments, Business, Tax, Trade, Telecommunications, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - Accomplishments, County visits, 1997-1998 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Accomplishments, Defense, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Accomplishments, Energy, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Accomplishments, Environment, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Accomplishments, Erie, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 9)
    - Accomplishments, Harrisburg, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 10)
    - Accomplishments, Interior, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - Accomplishments, Labor, 1998 (Box 294, Folder 12)
    - Accomplishments, Philadelphia, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 13)
    - Accomplishments, Pittsburgh, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 14)
    - Accomplishments, Transportation, 1991-1997 (Box 294, Folder 15)
    - Accomplishments, Veterans, 1995 (Box 294, Folder 16)
    - Advanced manufacturing training, 2005-2006 (Box 294, Folder 17)
    - African elephant conservation, 1997-1998 (Box 294, Folder 18)
    - Airline service in Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 294, Folder 19)
    - Allegheny National Forest, 1994-1996 (Box 294, Folder 20)
    - Allegheny National Forest, East Side Timber sale, 2000 (Box 294, Folder 21)
    - Allegheny National Forest, Recreation, 1998-1999 (Box 294, Folder 22)
    - AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 294, Folder 23)
    - American Postal Workers Union (APWU), 1989 (Box 294, Folder 24)
    - APWU, Greensburg Post Office, 2005 (Box 294, Folder 25)
    - Animal welfare, 1997-1998 (Box 294, Folder 26-31)
    - Animal welfare, Dear Colleagues letters, 1997-1998 (Box 294, Folder 32)
    - Armenian resolution, 1990 (Box 294, Folder 33)
    - Army/Navy football game, 1984 (Box 294, Folder 34)
    - Aspinwall Post Office, 2007-2008 (Box 294, Folder 35)
    - Avian flu, 1984-1986 (Box 294, Folder 36)
    - Bruce Babbit, Department of Interior confirmation hearing, 1993 (Box 294, Folder 37)
    - Bannering, NLRB, 2006 (Box 294, Folder 38)
    - Bear Protection Act, 1997-1998 (Box 294, Folder 39)
    - Benjamin Franklin Bicentennial, 1990 (Box 294, Folder 40)
    - Bill files, 1987-1990 (Box 294, Folder 41-42)
    - Bill files, 1987-1990 (Box 295, Folder 1-8)
    - Bipartisan group, 1996 (Box 295, Folder 9-10)
    - Black clergy of Philadelphia, 2006-2007 (Box 295, Folder 11)
    - Black Press of America, 2005 (Box 295, Folder 12)
    - Blind Entrepreneurs' Alliance, 2009 (Box 295, Folder 13)
    - Book tapes, 1984 (Box 295, Folder 14-17)
    - Boyers, Federal Investigations Processing Center closure, 1995 (Box 296, Folder 1-2)
    - Calendar of business, June 1996 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Calendar of business, June-July 1996 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Calendar of business, July 1996 (Box 296, Folder 5-6)
    - Brian Campbell, Crop disaster program benefits, 2008 (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - Canned hunt legislation, 1997 (Box 296, Folder 8)
    - Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1992-1993 (Box 296, Folder 9)
    - Censorship and communication, 1995 (Box 296, Folder 10)
    - Census Bureau, 1989 (Box 296, Folder 11)
    - Census overview, 1989-1990 (Box 296, Folder 12)
    - Chilean Exporters Association, 2007 (Box 296, Folder 13)
    - CIGNA insurance license for China, 1997 (Box 296, Folder 14)
    - Class Action Fairness Act, 1999-2000 (Box 296, Folder 15)
    - Fred Claycomb, Crop insurance, 2006 (Box 296, Folder 16)
    - Clean Vines Program, 2005 (Box 296, Folder 17)
    - Coin design, 1988-1990 (Box 296, Folder 18)
    - Colony Collapse Disorder Action Plan, 2007 (Box 296, Folder 19)
    - Commemorative postage stamp legislation, 1988 (Box 296, Folder 20)
    - Commerce, Science, and Transportation Committee, 1993 (Box 296, Folder 21)
    - Comparable worth, 1989 (Box 296, Folder 22)
    - Congressional Delegation (CODEL), Middle East, 1995-1996 (Box 296, Folder 23)